<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Varun A K</title>
    <link>https://akvarun.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Varun A K</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://akvarun.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://akvarun.github.io/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 19:41:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akvarun.github.io/first/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Varun AK! I&amp;rsquo;m currently a student of Computer Science and Engineering, and I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about all things related to technology. From a young age, I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinated by how computers work and how they can be used to solve complex problems.
During my studies, I&amp;rsquo;ve gained valuable experience in programming, web development, and database management. I&amp;rsquo;m always eager to learn new technologies and explore different areas within the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cybher physical system</title>
      <link>https://akvarun.github.io/notes/cps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akvarun.github.io/notes/cps/</guid>
      <description>Cyber-physical systems combine physical and computational components to interact with the real world in real-time. They improve efficiency, safety, and reliability in domains like healthcare, transportation, and manufacturing. CPS require expertise in computer science, control theory, and mechanical engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distributed System</title>
      <link>https://akvarun.github.io/notes/distributed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akvarun.github.io/notes/distributed/</guid>
      <description>A distributed system is a network of independent computers that work together by dividing tasks and coordinating actions through communication. It is used in various applications, such as e-commerce, social networks, and online gaming, but it can be challenging to design and implement due to the need for efficient communication, synchronization, and fault-tolerance..</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
